I saw this math Meme and so I thought I
would share it and I thought I would
explain it in case anybody doesn't get
it so it starts with a right triangle
with an angle X the side opposite of
that angle will call opposite the side
adjacent to it we'll call adjacent and
this side we'll call hypotenuse the S of
X is the ratio of the opposite over the
hypotenuse and the cosine of x is the
ratio of the adjacent over the
hypotenuse if we name the opposite side
a the adjacent side B and hypotenuse C
we can rewrite the S as a over C and the
cosine as B over C in the meme we have a
sin s x ring and a cosine squ X Ring
let's bring those two rings together
giving us sin^2 X plus cosine s x s of X
is a over C so sin squ of X would be a
over c^ 2 and then cosine is B over C
which would make this B over c^ 2 then
these squares can be distributed to all
the A's and the C's giving us a squ c s
plus b squ over c s now these have a
common denominator so we can just write
them as a single fraction now let's
rewrite this fraction let's bring the c^
S over and this is a right triangle so
that means that a s + b s is equal to
c^2 that's called the Pythagorean
theorem so now C2 over c s is equal to
one so when you have the sin squ ring
plus the cosine squ ring and they come
together they become one how wonderful